Robert Weston

Robert Weston

22040 128th PL SE Kent, WA 98031

253.797.7899 robert.d.weston@gmail.com

Skills

Management: Extensive experience working with management to train new employees. Assisting management weekly with inventory. Sitting down with management to discuss what they are doing right and could improve upon to create a better work experience. Leading other seasonals in completing the task at hand.

Sales: Excellent mental math and cash handling. Ensuring that every transaction is done correctly.

Customer Service: Helping guests with any issues during their visit. Ensuring that they receive the best service.

Computers: Seven years experience working on computers to troubleshoot problems either technical or hardware. Four years experience assembling computers for myself and/or friends and family.

Landscaping: Experience weeding, line trimming, soft and hard edging, hedging, top dressing, mowing, table sanding and varnishing, and pruning. Ability to recognize areas that need attention to keep the presentability of the park up to standard.

Experience

Renton Parks Department/ Seasonal Laborer

June 2017 - Current, Gene Coulon Park

My job with the Renton Parks department was to help with the upkeep of Gene Coulon Park. Following the Lead's instruction on the work that needed to be done around the park with landscape maintenance such as weeding, mowing, hedging, etc. Ensuring the park was clean as we would change the trashes around the park and made sure the lawns, paths, and parking lots were clear of trash. Patrolling the park to make sure the patrons were following the rules of the park.

REI/ Frontline Associate

July 2017 - December 2017, Bellevue

As a Frontline Associate, I worked the front registers providing personalized and knowledgeable customer service. I assisted the customers with any questions they had about products in store and ordering out of stock products. Processing returns for customers and resolving any issues they had with their products. Keeping the store stocked and presentable.

AMC Theaters/ Lead, Film Crew

June 2013 - April 2017, Westfield Southcenter

My job as an Lead was to be a leader in any position that I was assigned to work in. Delegating tasks to other employees to keep the facilities running smoothly and efficiently. Training new employees and current employees in the positions at the theater. Taking inventory at the theater weekly. Giving performance reviews to crew members. Working with management to help guests with any issues or needs they have while at the theater.

Bellevue College / Bachelors in Computer Science

September 2017 - Present, Bellevue, WA

Studying in their Computer Science program and set to graduate within the next year and a half. After graduating I am looking to pursue a career in software development and network security.

Education